[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the fourth baseball player to hit 600 home runs in the US major leagues (Babe Ruth, of course, was the first)?", "correct_answer": "Barry Bonds", "incorrect_answers": ["Ken Griffey, Jr.", "Willie Mays", "Sammy Sosa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of Italy was Don Vito Corleone born in Francis Ford Coppolas 1972 film The Godfather?", "correct_answer": "Sicily", "incorrect_answers": ["Venice", "Sardinia", "Rome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American-born soprano, nicknamed the Tennessee Nightingale, lived 1898-1947. She was nominated for an Oscar for One Night of Love.", "correct_answer": "Grace Moore", "incorrect_answers": ["Grace Toff", "Nellie Melba", "Melba Moore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Disneys second full length animated film?", "correct_answer": "Pinocchio", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Pan", "Cinderella", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three murders are committed in the Academy Award-winning film, There Will Be Blood.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the male reproductive organ which secretes an alkaline fluid?", "correct_answer": "prostate gland", "incorrect_answers": ["seminal vesicle", "cowpers gland", "penis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous movie contains a spoof  f the volleyball from Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "Scary Movie 2", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Shark Tale", "Finding Nemo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The recipe for the German chocolate cake did not originate in Germany, but in this country.", "correct_answer": "the USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "Spain", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals is considered to have the best immune system?", "correct_answer": "Vulture", "incorrect_answers": ["Kangaroo", "Asp", "Hyman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of scorpions usually consist of?", "correct_answer": "Insects", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Worms and maggots", "Plant matter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river that flows through Spain and Portugal is the longest river on the Iberian Peninsula?", "correct_answer": "Tagus", "incorrect_answers": ["Guadiana", "Duero", "Guadalquivir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Awards did the 1939 film Gone with the Wind win out of 13 nominations?", "correct_answer": "Ten", "incorrect_answers": ["Two", "None", "Five"]}]